Elizabeth E. May Papers 1997.0119
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV: Related Materials, undated, 1955-1996
  - Listing of Home Economists in Habilitation/ Rehabilitation/ Human Services - University of Missouri, undated (Box 8, Folder 480)
  - Magazine Stories, undated (Box 8, Folder 481)
  - National Tuberculosis Association
    - Correspondence/ Speech- “What Makes A Board Tick”, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 485)
    - “What Makes a Board Tick” -speech and correspondence about publication, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 486)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles
    - Handicapped, undated (Box 8, Folder 487)
    - Home/ Family, undated (Box 8, Folder 488)
    - Various topics, undated (Box 8, Folder 489)
    - Women, undated (Box 8, Folder 490)
  - On Your Own - for disabled and elderly, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 491)
  - 100 Years Of Women at UCONN, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 492)
  - Poems, Clippings, and Pamphlets, undated (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - Printed Material, undated (Box 8, Folder 484)
  - Programs for the Handicapped Office for Handicapped Individuals, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 493)
  - “Questions for a Religious Inquiry”, undated (Box 8, Folder 494)
  - Scrapbook Material, undated (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - Second National Trails Symposium -correspondence and program, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 495)
  - Self Help Items and Aids for Easier Living, undated (Box 9, Folder 497)
  - The Social and Rehabilitation Record, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 498)
  - Speeches
    - Employment of Mothers Economic Workshop notes and research, undated (Box 9, Folder 499)
    - Liberal Arts -clippings and articles, undated (Box 9, Folder 500)
  - State Universities and Faculty, undated (Box 9, Folder 501)
  - University of Missouri
    - College of Home Economics, undated (Box 9, Folder 502)
  - Untitled Speeches and Notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 503)
  - Volunteering
    - Speech by E.E. May -“The Volunteer in Today's Culture”, undated (Box 9, Folder 504)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 505)
    - Articles, 1955-1962 (Box 9, Folder 506)
    - “Working with Volunteers” -pamphlet, undated (Box 9, Folder 507)
  - Wings of VGRS (Easy Wear Clothing), undated (Box 9, Folder 508)
  - Women--A Human resource (grant proposal, Eva Hansl), undated (Box 11)
  - Addresses Relating to Books, undated (Box 9, Folder 509)
- Series V: Photographs, undated, 1901-1994
  - Eckhardt Family (Box 10)
    - Elizabeth E. May, 1901-1993
    - Elizabeth E. May (daughter and grandchildren), 1940-1994
    - Festivals and Fairs, undated
    - Pictures and Information, undated
    - Pocahontas County Fair, 1926
  - Handicapped Homemakers Project (29 large mounted black & white images), undated (Box 11)
  - Photographs (unsorted), undated (Box 12)